<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>iCFree</title>
    <link>https://icfree.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on iCFree</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://icfree.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://icfree.org/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icfree.org/home/</guid>
      <description>iCFree
Improved cell-free systems to accelerate therapeutic proteins production at minimal cost
  Funded by one of the 5 grand challenges launched by the PIA program of the French government Biomedicines: improving yields and controlling production costs
Healthcare systems are increasingly dependent on access to critical, high-value proteins, which are often environmentally damaging and complex to obtain domestically. The emergence of functionalized and customized proteins is enabling a radical transformation of therapies, which are becoming more individualized and complex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://icfree.org/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icfree.org/news/</guid>
      <description>A collection of articles, blogs and videos featuring the iCFree project</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://icfree.org/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icfree.org/partners/</guid>
      <description>To fulfill iCFree&#39;s ambitious vision, the consortium is made up of 3 research insititutes and 1 SME with complementary expertise in cell-free systems and protein production. Those are some of France&#39;s most relevant players in the fields.    The MICALIS institute (INRAE, AgroParisTech, Univ. of Paris Saclay) has several years of experience and published records in optimizing prokaryotic cell-free systems with machine learning for biomanufacturing and developing biosensors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
